<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="charsheet.xsl"?>
<chargen>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Cleric</class>
			<race>Half-Elf</race>
			<caster>1</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Falak Aran</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>43</age>
			<ht>67</ht>
			<wt>100</wt>
			<align>Chaotic Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>12</STR>
			<CON>9</CON>
			<INT>12</INT>
			<WIS>13</WIS>
			<DEX>15</DEX>
			<CHA>6</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>10</pois1>
				<pois2>10</pois2>
				<pois3>10</pois3>
				<pois4>9</pois4>
				<pois5>9</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>13</petr1>
				<petr2>13</petr2>
				<petr3>13</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>13</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>15</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>15</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>2</hp1>
				<hp2>6</hp2>
				<hp3>14</hp3>
				<hp4>20</hp4>
				<hp5>24</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>18</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>6</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>-1</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>4</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Chalk Powder</item>
				<item>Lantern</item>
				<item>Maul</item>
				<item>Ring Mail</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>180</gold>
			<wdie>d8</wdie>
		</props>
		<spells>
			<L1>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Sanctuary </s_name>
					<s_text>When the cleric casts a Sanctuary spell, any opponent must make a saving throw versus magic in order to strike or otherwise attack him or her. If the saving throw is not made, the creature will attack another and totally ignore the cleric protected by the spell. If the saving throw is made, the cleric is subject to normal attack process including dicing for weapons to hit, saving throws, damage. Note that this spell does not prevent the operation of area attacks (Fireball, Ice Storm, etc.). During the period of protection afforded by this spell, the cleric cannot take offensive action, but he or she may use non-attack spells or otherwise act in any way which does not violate the prohibition against offensive action, This allows the cleric to heal wounds, for example, or to bless, perform an augury, chant, cast a light in the area (not upon on opponent!), and so on, The components of the spell include the cleric's holy/unholy symbol and a small silver mirror. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.4</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2+n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L1>
			<L2>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Light </s_name>
					<s_text>This spell causes excitation of molecules so as to make them brightly luminous. The light thus caused is equal to torch light in brightness, but its sphere is limited to 4" in diameter. It lasts for the duration indicated (7 turns at 1st experience level, 8 at 2nd, 9 at 3rd, etc.) or until the caster utters a word to extinguish the light. The Light spell is reversible, causing darkness in the same area and under the same conditions, except the blackness persists for only one half the duration that light would last. If this spell is cast upon a creature, the applicable magic resistance and saving throw dice rolls must be made. Success indicates that the spell affects the area immediately behind the creature, rather than the creature itself. In all other cases, the spell takes effect where the caster directs as long as he or she has a line of sight or unobstructed path for the spell; fight can spring from air, rock, metal, wood, or almost any similar substance.</s_text>
					<s_cast>0.4</s_cast>
					<s_dura>60+n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L2>
			<L3>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Snake Charm </s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is cast, a hypnotic pattern is set up which causes one or more snakes to cease all activity except a semi-erect postured swaying movement. If the snakes are charmed while in a torpor, the duration of the spell is 3 to 6 turns (d4 + 2); if the snakes are not torpid, but are not aroused and angry, the charm lasts 1 to 3 turns; if the snakes are angry and/or attacking, the snake charm spell will last from 5 to 8 melee rounds (d4+4). The cleric casting the spell can charm snakes whose hit points are less than or equal to those of the cleric. On the average, a 1st level cleric could charm snakes with a total of 4 or 5 hit points; a 2nd level cleric 9 hit points, a 3rd level 13 or 14 hit points, etc. The hit points can represent a single snake or several of the reptiles, but the total hit points cannot exceed those of the cleric casting the spell. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.5</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Special</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L3>
			<L4>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Cure Light Wounds</s_name>
					<s_text>Upon laying his or her hand upon a creature, the cleric causes from 1 to 8 hit points of wound or other injury damage to the creature's body to be healed. This healing will not affect creatures without corporeal bodies, nor will it cure wounds of creatures not living or those which can be harmed only by iron, silver, and/or magical weapons. Its reverse, Cause Light Wounds, operates in the same manner; and if a person is avoiding this touch, a melee combat "to hit" die is rolled to determine if the cleric's hand strikes the opponent and causes such a wound. Note that cured wounds are permanent only insofar as the creature does not sustain further damage, and that caused wounds will heal - or can be cured - just as any normal injury will. Caused light wounds are 1 to 8 hit points of damage. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.5</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Permanent</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Silence, 15' Radius</s_name>
					<s_text>Upon casting this spell, complete silence prevails in the area of its effect. All sound is stopped, so all conversation is impossible, spells cannot be cast and no noise whatsoever issues forth, The spell can be cast into the air or upon an object. The spell of Silence lasts for 2 rounds for each level of experience of the cleric, i.e. 2 rounds at 1st level, 4 at 2nd, 6 at 3rd, 8 at 4th and so forth. The spell can be cast upon a creature, and the effect will then radiate from the creature and move as it moves. If the creature is unwilling, it saves against the spell, and if the saving throw is made, the spell effect locates about one foot behind the target creature. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.5</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L4>
			<L5>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Slow Poison</s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is placed upon a poisoned individual it greatly slows the effects of any venom, even causing a supposedly dead individual to have life restored if it is cast upon the victim within a number of turns less than or equal to the level of experience of the cleric after the poisoning was suffered. i.e. a victim poisoned up to 10 turns previously could be temporarily saved by a 10th or higher level cleric who cast Slow Poison upon the victim. While this spell does not neutralize the venom, it does prevent it from substantially harming the individual for the duration of its magic, but each turn the poisoned creature will lose 1 hit point from the effect of the venom (although the victim will never go below 1 hit point while the Slow Poison spell's duration lasts). Thus, in the example above, the victim poisoned 10 turns previously has only 10 hit points, so when the 10th level cleric casts the spell, the victim remains with 1 hit point until the spell duration expires, and hopefully during that period a full cure can be accomplished. The material components of this spell are the cleric's holy/unholy symbol and a bud of garlic which must be crushed and smeared on the victim's bare feet. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>60n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Continual Light</s_name>
					<s_text>This spell is similar to a Light spell, except that it lasts until negated (by a Continual Darkness or Dispel Magic spell) and its brightness is very great, being nearly as illuminating as full daylight. It can be cast into air, onto an object, or at a creature, In the third case, the Continual Light affects the space about one foot behind the creature if the latter makes its saving throw. Note that this spell will blind a creature if it is successfully cast upon the visual organs, for example. Its reverse causes complete absence of light. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.6</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Permanent</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L5>
		</spells>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Fighter</class>
			<race>Dwarf</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Burchard Bornin</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>54</age>
			<ht>53</ht>
			<wt>135</wt>
			<align>Neutral Good</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>9</STR>
			<CON>13</CON>
			<INT>13</INT>
			<WIS>11</WIS>
			<DEX>15</DEX>
			<CHA>15</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>11</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>15</petr1>
				<petr2>15</petr2>
				<petr3>14</petr3>
				<petr4>14</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>16</wand1>
				<wand2>16</wand2>
				<wand3>15</wand3>
				<wand4>15</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>17</brea1>
				<brea2>17</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>13</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>17</spel1>
				<spel2>17</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>13</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>6</hp1>
				<hp2>12</hp2>
				<hp3>14</hp3>
				<hp4>21</hp4>
				<hp5>31</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>16</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>6</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>-1</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>1</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Flint and Steel</item>
				<item>50' Rope</item>
				<item>Hand Axe</item>
				<item>Ring Mail</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>70</gold>
			<wdie>d6</wdie>
		</props>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Thief</class>
			<race>Elf</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>1</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Fendarel ["Ce'nedra"]</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>114</age>
			<ht>65</ht>
			<wt>100</wt>
			<align>Neutral Good</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>8</STR>
			<CON>5</CON>
			<INT>3</INT>
			<WIS>11</WIS>
			<DEX>14</DEX>
			<CHA>11</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>13</pois1>
				<pois2>13</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>12</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>12</petr1>
				<petr2>12</petr2>
				<petr3>12</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>11</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>14</wand4>
				<wand5>12</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>2</hp1>
				<hp2>6</hp2>
				<hp3>12</hp3>
				<hp4>14</hp4>
				<hp5>16</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>19</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>8</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-2</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>1</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Grappling Hook</item>
				<item>Small Iron Box</item>
				<item>Dagger</item>
				<item>Padded Armor</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>100</gold>
			<wdie>d4</wdie>
		</props>
		<skills>
			<pockets>
				<pock1>35</pock1>
				<pock2>40</pock2>
				<pock3>45</pock3>
				<pock4>50</pock4>
				<pock5>55</pock5>
			</pockets>
			<locks>
				<lock1>20</lock1>
				<lock2>24</lock2>
				<lock3>28</lock3>
				<lock4>32</lock4>
				<lock5>37</lock5>
			</locks>
			<traps>
				<trap1>20</trap1>
				<trap2>25</trap2>
				<trap3>30</trap3>
				<trap4>35</trap4>
				<trap5>40</trap5>
			</traps>
			<sneak>
				<sneak1>20</sneak1>
				<sneak2>26</sneak2>
				<sneak3>32</sneak3>
				<sneak4>38</sneak4>
				<sneak5>45</sneak5>
			</sneak>
			<hide>
				<hide1>20</hide1>
				<hide2>25</hide2>
				<hide3>30</hide3>
				<hide4>35</hide4>
				<hide5>41</hide5>
			</hide>
			<listen>
				<listen1>15</listen1>
				<listen2>15</listen2>
				<listen3>20</listen3>
				<listen4>20</listen4>
				<listen5>25</listen5>
			</listen>
			<climb>
				<climb1>85</climb1>
				<climb2>86</climb2>
				<climb3>87</climb3>
				<climb4>88</climb4>
				<climb5>90</climb5>
			</climb>
			<read>
				<read1>0</read1>
				<read2>0</read2>
				<read3>0</read3>
				<read4>20</read4>
				<read5>25</read5>
			</read>
		</skills>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Cleric</class>
			<race>Half-Elf</race>
			<caster>1</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Moira Adamma</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>43</age>
			<ht>63</ht>
			<wt>130</wt>
			<align>Lawful Evil</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>9</STR>
			<CON>11</CON>
			<INT>14</INT>
			<WIS>9</WIS>
			<DEX>9</DEX>
			<CHA>13</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>10</pois1>
				<pois2>10</pois2>
				<pois3>10</pois3>
				<pois4>9</pois4>
				<pois5>9</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>13</petr1>
				<petr2>13</petr2>
				<petr3>13</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>13</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>15</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>15</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>6</hp1>
				<hp2>8</hp2>
				<hp3>10</hp3>
				<hp4>12</hp4>
				<hp5>18</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>18</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>7</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>1</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Large pouch</item>
				<item>50' Rope</item>
				<item>Sling</item>
				<item>Studded Leather Armor</item>
				<item>30 Sling Bullets</item>
				<item>Sling Bullet Sack</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>110</gold>
			<wdie>d4+1</wdie>
		</props>
		<spells>
			<L1>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Protection From Evil </s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is cast, it acts as if it were a magical armour upon the recipient. The protection encircles the recipient at a one foot distance, thus preventing bodily contact by creatures of an enchanted or conjured nature such as aerial servants, demons, devils, djinn, efreet, elementals, imps, invisible stalkers, night hags, quasits, salamanders, water weirds, wind walkers, and xorn. Summoned animals or monsters are similarly hedged from the protected creature. Furthermore, any and all attacks launched by evil creatures incur a penalty of -2 from dice rolls "to hit" the protected creature, and any saving throws caused by such attacks are made at +2 on the protected creature's dice. This spell can be reversed to become Protection From Good, although it still keeps out enchanted evil creatures as well. To complete this spell, the cleric must truce a 3' diameter circle upon the floor (or ground) with holy water for Protection From Evil, with blood for Protection From Good - or in the air using burning incense or smouldering dung with respect to evil/good. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.4</s_cast>
					<s_dura>5n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L1>
			<L2>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Detect Evil </s_name>
					<s_text>This is a spell which discovers emanations of evil, or of good in the case of the reverse spell, from any creature or object. For example, evil alignment or an evilly cursed object will radiate evil, but a hidden trop or an unintelligent viper will not. The duration of a Detect Evil (or Detect Good) spell is 1 turn + ½ turn (5 rounds, or 5 minutes) per level of the cleric. Thus a cleric of 1st level of experience can cast a spell with a 1½ turn duration, at 2nd level a 2 turn duration, 2½ at 3rd, etc. The spell has a path of detection 1" wide in the direction in which the cleric is facing. It requires the use of the cleric's holy (or unholy) symbol as its material component, with the cleric holding it before him or her. </s_text>
					<s_cast>1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>10+5n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L2>
			<L3>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Know Alignment </s_name>
					<s_text>A Know Alignment spell enables the cleric to exactly read the aura of a person - human, semi-human, or non-human. This will reveal the exact alignment of the person. Up to 10 persons can be examined with this spell. The reverse totally obscures alignment, even from this spell, of a single person for 1 turn, two persons for 5 rounds, etc. Certain magical devices will negate the ability to Know Alignment. </s_text>
					<s_cast>1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>10</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L3>
			<L4>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Resist Cold</s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is placed on a creature by a cleric, the creature's body is inured to cold. The recipient can stand zero degrees Fahrenheit without discomfort, even totally nude. Greater cold, such as that produced by a sword of cold, ice storm, cold wand, or white dragon's breath, must be saved against. All saving throws against cold are made with a bonus of +3, and damage sustained is one-half (if the saving throw is not made) or one-quarter (if the saving throw is made) of damage normal from that attack form. The resistance lasts for 1 turn per level of experience of the caster. A pinch of sulphur is necessary to complete this spell. </s_text>
					<s_cast>1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>10n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Speak With Animals </s_name>
					<s_text>By employing this spell, the cleric is empowered to comprehend and communicate with any warm or cold-blooded animal which is not mindless (such as an amoeba). The cleric is able to ask questions, receive answers, and generally be on amicable terms with the animal. This ability lasts for 2 melee rounds for each level of experience of the cleric employing the spell. Even if the bent of the animal is opposite to that of the cleric (evil/good, good/evil), it and any others of the same kind with it will not attack while the spell lasts. If the animal is neutral or of the some general bent as the cleric (evil/evil, good/good), there is a possibility that the animal, and its like associates, will do some favour or service for the cleric. This possibility will be determined by the referee by consulting a special reaction chart, using the charisma of the cleric and his actions as the major determinants. Note that this spell differs from speak with monsters (q.v.), for it allows conversation only with basically normal, non-fantastic creatures such as apes, bears, cats, dogs, elephants, and so on. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.5</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L4>
			<L5>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Spiritual Hammer</s_name>
					<s_text>By calling upon his or her deity, the cleric casting a Spiritual Hammer spell brings into existence a field of force which is shaped vaguely like a hammer. This area of force is hammer-sized, and as long as the cleric who invoked it concentrates upon the hammer, it will strike at any opponent within its range as desired by the cleric. The force area strikes as a magical weapon equal to one plus per 3 levels of experience of the spell caster for purposes of being able to strike creatures, although it has no magical plusses whatsoever "to hit", and the damage it causes when it scores a hit is exactly the same as a normal war hammer, i.e. 1-6 versus opponents of man-sire or smaller, 1-4 upon larger opponents. Furthermore, the hammer strikes at exactly the same level as the cleric controlling it, just as if the cleric was personally wielding the weapon. As soon as the cleric ceases concentration, the Spiritual Hammer is dispelled. Note: If the cleric is behind an opponent, the force can strike from this position, thus gaining all bonuses for such an attack and negating defensive protections such as shield and dexterity. The material component of this spell is a normal war hammer which the cleric must hurl towards opponents whilst uttering a plea to his or her deity. The hammer disappears when the spell is cast. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.5</s_cast>
					<s_dura>n</s_dura>
					<s_save>Special</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Remove Curse</s_name>
					<s_text>Upon casting this spell, the cleric is usually able to remove a curse - whether it be on an object, a person, or in the form of some undesired sending or evil presence. Note that the Remove Curse spell will not affect a cursed shield, weapon or suit of armour, for example, although the spell will typically enable the person afflicted with any such cursed item to be rid of it. The reverse of the spell is not permanent; the Bestow Curse lasts for 1 turn for every level of experience of the cleric using the spell. It will lower one ability of the victim to 3 (your DM will determine which by random selection) 50% of the time; reduce the victim's "to hit" and saving throw probabilities by -4 25% of the time; or make the victim 50% likely per turn to drop whatever he, she, or it is holding (or simply do nothing in the case of creatures not using tools) 25% of the time. It is possible for a cleric to devise his or her own curse, and it should be similar in power to those shown. Consult your referee. The target of a Bestow Curse spell must be touched. If the victim is touched, a saving throw is still applicable; and if it is successful, the effect is negated. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.6</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Permanent</s_dura>
					<s_save>Special</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L5>
		</spells>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Fighter</class>
			<race>Elf</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Porras Ewanne</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>143</age>
			<ht>64</ht>
			<wt>100</wt>
			<align>Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>9</STR>
			<CON>8</CON>
			<INT>6</INT>
			<WIS>10</WIS>
			<DEX>12</DEX>
			<CHA>4</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>11</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>15</petr1>
				<petr2>15</petr2>
				<petr3>14</petr3>
				<petr4>14</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>16</wand1>
				<wand2>16</wand2>
				<wand3>15</wand3>
				<wand4>15</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>17</brea1>
				<brea2>17</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>13</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>17</spel1>
				<spel2>17</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>13</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>7</hp1>
				<hp2>14</hp2>
				<hp3>17</hp3>
				<hp4>21</hp4>
				<hp5>28</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>16</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>6</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-4</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>1</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Prayer Beads</item>
				<item>Large Sack</item>
				<item>Club</item>
				<item>Scale Mail</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>80</gold>
			<wdie>d6</wdie>
		</props>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Thief</class>
			<race>Half-Orc</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>1</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Nantes Nerissa</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>21</age>
			<ht>70</ht>
			<wt>139</wt>
			<align>Chaotic Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>7</STR>
			<CON>9</CON>
			<INT>15</INT>
			<WIS>15</WIS>
			<DEX>12</DEX>
			<CHA>8</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>13</pois1>
				<pois2>13</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>12</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>12</petr1>
				<petr2>12</petr2>
				<petr3>12</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>11</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>14</wand4>
				<wand5>12</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>4</hp1>
				<hp2>9</hp2>
				<hp3>10</hp3>
				<hp4>12</hp4>
				<hp5>13</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>19</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>7</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>1</doors>
			<lgbb>0</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Large pouch</item>
				<item>Pint of Ale</item>
				<item>Greatsword</item>
				<item>Ring Mail</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>40</gold>
			<wdie>2d6</wdie>
		</props>
		<skills>
			<pockets>
				<pock1>25</pock1>
				<pock2>30</pock2>
				<pock3>35</pock3>
				<pock4>40</pock4>
				<pock5>45</pock5>
			</pockets>
			<locks>
				<lock1>30</lock1>
				<lock2>34</lock2>
				<lock3>38</lock3>
				<lock4>42</lock4>
				<lock5>47</lock5>
			</locks>
			<traps>
				<trap1>25</trap1>
				<trap2>30</trap2>
				<trap3>35</trap3>
				<trap4>40</trap4>
				<trap5>45</trap5>
			</traps>
			<sneak>
				<sneak1>10</sneak1>
				<sneak2>16</sneak2>
				<sneak3>22</sneak3>
				<sneak4>28</sneak4>
				<sneak5>35</sneak5>
			</sneak>
			<hide>
				<hide1>10</hide1>
				<hide2>15</hide2>
				<hide3>20</hide3>
				<hide4>25</hide4>
				<hide5>31</hide5>
			</hide>
			<listen>
				<listen1>15</listen1>
				<listen2>15</listen2>
				<listen3>20</listen3>
				<listen4>20</listen4>
				<listen5>25</listen5>
			</listen>
			<climb>
				<climb1>90</climb1>
				<climb2>91</climb2>
				<climb3>92</climb3>
				<climb4>93</climb4>
				<climb5>95</climb5>
			</climb>
			<read>
				<read1>0</read1>
				<read2>0</read2>
				<read3>0</read3>
				<read4>10</read4>
				<read5>15</read5>
			</read>
		</skills>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Wizard</class>
			<race>Human</race>
			<caster>1</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Pil-Galdur Vanya</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>28</age>
			<ht>71</ht>
			<wt>130</wt>
			<align>Lawful Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>14</STR>
			<CON>13</CON>
			<INT>10</INT>
			<WIS>13</WIS>
			<DEX>11</DEX>
			<CHA>13</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>14</pois3>
				<pois4>14</pois4>
				<pois5>14</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>13</petr1>
				<petr2>13</petr2>
				<petr3>13</petr3>
				<petr4>13</petr4>
				<petr5>13</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>11</wand1>
				<wand2>11</wand2>
				<wand3>11</wand3>
				<wand4>11</wand4>
				<wand5>11</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>15</brea1>
				<brea2>15</brea2>
				<brea3>15</brea3>
				<brea4>15</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>15</spel1>
				<spel2>15</spel2>
				<spel3>15</spel3>
				<spel4>15</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>2</hp1>
				<hp2>5</hp2>
				<hp3>6</hp3>
				<hp4>7</hp4>
				<hp5>11</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>20</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>10</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>0</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>7</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Prayer Beads</item>
				<item>Bag of Shot</item>
				<item>Sling</item>
				<item>Wizard Robes</item>
				<item>30 Sling Bullets</item>
				<item>Sling Bullet Sack</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>90</gold>
			<wdie>d4+1</wdie>
		</props>
		<spells>
			<L1>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Nystul's Magic Aura</s_name>
					<s_text> By means of this spell any one item of a weight of 50 g.p. per level of experience of the spell caster can be given an aura which will be noticed if detection of magic is exercised upon the object. If the object bearing the Nystul's Magic Aura is actually held by the creature detecting for a dweomer, he, she or it is entitled to a saving throw versus magic, and if this throw is successful, the creature knows that the aura has been placed to mislead the unwary. Otherwise, the aura is simply magical, but no amount of testing will reveal what the magic is. The component for this spell is a small square of silk which must be passed over the object to bear the aura. </s_text>
					<s_cast>1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>n days</s_dura>
					<s_save>Special</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L1>
			<L2>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Spider Climb</s_name>
					<s_text> A Spider Climb spell enables the recipient to climb and travel upon vertical surfaces just as a giant spider is able to do, i.e. at 3" movement rate, or even hang upside down from ceilings. Note that the affected creature must have bare hands and feet in order to climb in this manner. During the course of the spell the recipient cannot handle objects which weigh less than 50 g.p., for such objects will stick to the creature's hands/feet, so a magic-user will find it virtually impossible to cast spells if under a Spider Climb dweomer. The material components of this spell are a drop of bitumen and a live spider, both of which must be eaten by the spell recipient. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>1+n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L2>
			<L3>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Invisibility</s_name>
					<s_text>This spell causes the recipient to vanish from sight and not be detectable by normal vision or even infravision. Of course, the invisible creature is not magically silenced with respect to noises normal to it. The spell remains In effect until it is magically broken or dispelled, or the magic-user or the other recipient cancels it or until he, she or it attacks any creature. Thus, the spell caster or recipient could open doors, talk, eat, climb stairs, etc., but if any form of attack is made, the invisible creature immediately becomes visible, although this will allow the first attack by the creature because of the former invisibility. Even the allies of the spell recipient cannot see the invisible creature, or his, her or its gear, unless these allies can normally see invisible things or employ magic to do so. Note that all highly intelligent creatures with 10 or more hit dice, or levels of experience, or the equivalent in intelligence/dice/levels have a chance to automatically detect invisible objects. The material components of the Invisibility spell are an eyelash and a bit of gum arabic, the former encased in the latter. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.2</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Special</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L3>
			<L4>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Unseen Servant</s_name>
					<s_text>The Unseen Servant is a non-visible valet, a butler to step and fetch, open doors and hold chairs, as well as to clean and mend. The spell creates a force which is not strong, but which obeys the command of the magic-user. It can carry only light-weight items - a maximum of 200 gold pieces weight suspended, twice that amount moving across a relatively friction-free surface such as a smooth stone or wood floor. It can only open normal doors, drawers, lids, etc. The Unseen Servant cannot fight nor can it be killed, as it is a force rather than a creature. It can be magically dispelled, or eliminated after taking 6 hit points of magical damage. The material components of the spell are a piece of string and a bit of wood. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>60+10n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Knock</s_name>
					<s_text>The Knock spell will open stuck or held or wizard-locked doors. It will also open barred or otherwise locked doors. It causes secret doors to open. The Knock spell will also open locked or trick-opening boxes or chests. It will loose shackles or chains as well. If it is used to open a wizard-locked door, the Knock does not remove the former spell, but it simply suspends its functioning for 1 turn. In all other cases, the Knock will permanently open locks or welds - although the former could be closed and locked again thereafter. It will not raise bars or similar impediments (such as a portcullis). The spell will perform two functions, but if a door is locked, barred, and held, opening it will require two Knock spells. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Special</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L4>
			<L5>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Protection from Evil</s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is cast, it acts as if it were a magical armour upon the recipient. The protection encircles the recipient at a one foot distance, thus preventing bodily contact by creatures of an enchanted or conjured nature such as aerial servants, demons, devils, djinn, efreet, elementals, imps, invisible stalkers, night hags, quasits, salamanders, water weirds, wind walkers, and xorn. Summoned animals or monsters are similarly hedged from the protected creature. Furthermore, any and all attacks launched by evil creatures incur a penalty of -2 from dice rolls "to hit" the protected creature, and any saving throws caused by such attacks are made at +2 on the protected creature's dice. This spell can be reversed to become Protection From Good, although it still keeps out enchanted evil creatures as well. To complete this spell, the cleric must truce a 3' diameter circle upon the floor (or ground) with holy water for Protection From Evil, with blood for Protection From Good - or in the air using burning incense or smouldering dung with respect to evil/good. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Flame Arrow</s_name>
					<s_text>Once the magic-user has cast this spell. he or she is able to touch one arrow or crossbow bolt (quarrel) per segment for the duration of the Flame Arrow. Each such missile so touched becomes magic, although it gains no bonuses "to hit". Each such missile must be discharged within 1 round, for after that period flame consumes it entirely, and the magic is lost. Fiery missiles will certainly have normal probabilities of causing combustion. and any creature subject to additional fire damage will suffer +1 hit point of damage from any flame arrow which hits it. The material components for this spell are a drop of oil and a small piece of flint.</s_text>
					<s_cast>0.3</s_cast>
					<s_dura>n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L5>
		</spells>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Thief</class>
			<race>Gnome</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>1</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Orenda Lailah</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>90</age>
			<ht>43</ht>
			<wt>80</wt>
			<align>Lawful Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>15</STR>
			<CON>14</CON>
			<INT>16</INT>
			<WIS>14</WIS>
			<DEX>12</DEX>
			<CHA>8</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>13</pois1>
				<pois2>13</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>12</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>12</petr1>
				<petr2>12</petr2>
				<petr3>12</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>11</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>14</wand4>
				<wand5>12</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>2</hp1>
				<hp2>5</hp2>
				<hp3>8</hp3>
				<hp4>9</hp4>
				<hp5>14</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>19</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>7</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>7</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Shovel</item>
				<item>10' Ladder</item>
				<item>Greatsword</item>
				<item>Studded Leather Armor</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>170</gold>
			<wdie>2d6</wdie>
		</props>
		<skills>
			<pockets>
				<pock1>30</pock1>
				<pock2>35</pock2>
				<pock3>40</pock3>
				<pock4>45</pock4>
				<pock5>50</pock5>
			</pockets>
			<locks>
				<lock1>30</lock1>
				<lock2>34</lock2>
				<lock3>38</lock3>
				<lock4>42</lock4>
				<lock5>47</lock5>
			</locks>
			<traps>
				<trap1>30</trap1>
				<trap2>35</trap2>
				<trap3>40</trap3>
				<trap4>45</trap4>
				<trap5>50</trap5>
			</traps>
			<sneak>
				<sneak1>15</sneak1>
				<sneak2>21</sneak2>
				<sneak3>27</sneak3>
				<sneak4>33</sneak4>
				<sneak5>40</sneak5>
			</sneak>
			<hide>
				<hide1>15</hide1>
				<hide2>20</hide2>
				<hide3>25</hide3>
				<hide4>30</hide4>
				<hide5>36</hide5>
			</hide>
			<listen>
				<listen1>20</listen1>
				<listen2>20</listen2>
				<listen3>25</listen3>
				<listen4>25</listen4>
				<listen5>30</listen5>
			</listen>
			<climb>
				<climb1>70</climb1>
				<climb2>71</climb2>
				<climb3>72</climb3>
				<climb4>73</climb4>
				<climb5>75</climb5>
			</climb>
			<read>
				<read1>0</read1>
				<read2>0</read2>
				<read3>0</read3>
				<read4>20</read4>
				<read5>25</read5>
			</read>
		</skills>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Thief</class>
			<race>Elf</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>1</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Vidar Valerius</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>118</age>
			<ht>55</ht>
			<wt>80</wt>
			<align>Neutral Evil</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>12</STR>
			<CON>6</CON>
			<INT>13</INT>
			<WIS>10</WIS>
			<DEX>10</DEX>
			<CHA>8</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>13</pois1>
				<pois2>13</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>12</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>12</petr1>
				<petr2>12</petr2>
				<petr3>12</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>11</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>14</wand4>
				<wand5>12</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>6</hp1>
				<hp2>10</hp2>
				<hp3>16</hp3>
				<hp4>20</hp4>
				<hp5>23</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>19</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>8</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-2</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>4</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>10' Ladder</item>
				<item>Chalk Powder</item>
				<item>Sling</item>
				<item>Padded Armor</item>
				<item>30 Sling Bullets</item>
				<item>Sling Bullet Sack</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>100</gold>
			<wdie>d4+1</wdie>
		</props>
		<skills>
			<pockets>
				<pock1>25</pock1>
				<pock2>30</pock2>
				<pock3>35</pock3>
				<pock4>40</pock4>
				<pock5>45</pock5>
			</pockets>
			<locks>
				<lock1>15</lock1>
				<lock2>19</lock2>
				<lock3>23</lock3>
				<lock4>27</lock4>
				<lock5>32</lock5>
			</locks>
			<traps>
				<trap1>10</trap1>
				<trap2>15</trap2>
				<trap3>20</trap3>
				<trap4>25</trap4>
				<trap5>30</trap5>
			</traps>
			<sneak>
				<sneak1>5</sneak1>
				<sneak2>11</sneak2>
				<sneak3>17</sneak3>
				<sneak4>23</sneak4>
				<sneak5>30</sneak5>
			</sneak>
			<hide>
				<hide1>15</hide1>
				<hide2>20</hide2>
				<hide3>25</hide3>
				<hide4>30</hide4>
				<hide5>36</hide5>
			</hide>
			<listen>
				<listen1>15</listen1>
				<listen2>15</listen2>
				<listen3>20</listen3>
				<listen4>20</listen4>
				<listen5>25</listen5>
			</listen>
			<climb>
				<climb1>85</climb1>
				<climb2>86</climb2>
				<climb3>87</climb3>
				<climb4>88</climb4>
				<climb5>90</climb5>
			</climb>
			<read>
				<read1>0</read1>
				<read2>0</read2>
				<read3>0</read3>
				<read4>20</read4>
				<read5>25</read5>
			</read>
		</skills>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Wizard</class>
			<race>Human</race>
			<caster>1</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Farhon Fadelin</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>30</age>
			<ht>68</ht>
			<wt>130</wt>
			<align>Chaotic Evil</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>11</STR>
			<CON>10</CON>
			<INT>14</INT>
			<WIS>5</WIS>
			<DEX>12</DEX>
			<CHA>13</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>14</pois3>
				<pois4>14</pois4>
				<pois5>14</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>13</petr1>
				<petr2>13</petr2>
				<petr3>13</petr3>
				<petr4>13</petr4>
				<petr5>13</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>11</wand1>
				<wand2>11</wand2>
				<wand3>11</wand3>
				<wand4>11</wand4>
				<wand5>11</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>15</brea1>
				<brea2>15</brea2>
				<brea3>15</brea3>
				<brea4>15</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>15</spel1>
				<spel2>15</spel2>
				<spel3>15</spel3>
				<spel4>15</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>2</hp1>
				<hp2>5</hp2>
				<hp3>6</hp3>
				<hp4>10</hp4>
				<hp5>13</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>20</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>10</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>0</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>2</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Small pouch</item>
				<item>Pickaxe</item>
				<item>Sling</item>
				<item>Wizard Robes</item>
				<item>30 Sling Bullets</item>
				<item>Sling Bullet Sack</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>90</gold>
			<wdie>d4+1</wdie>
		</props>
		<spells>
			<L1>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Dancing Lights</s_name>
					<s_text>When a dancing lights spell is cast, the magic-user creates, at his or her option, from 1 to 4 lights which resemble either A) torches and/or lanterns (and cast that amount of light), B) glowing spheres of light (such as evidenced by will-o-wisps), or C) one faintly glowing, vaguely man-like shape, somewhat similar to that of a creature from the Elemental Plane of Fire. The Dancing Lights move as the spell caster desires, forward or back, straight or turning corners, without concentration upon such movement by the magic-user. The spell will wink out if the range or duration is exceeded. Range is a base of 4" plus 1" for each level of the magic-user who cast the spell. Duration is 2 melee rounds per level of the spell caster . The material component of this spell is either a bit of phosphorus or wytchwood or a glowworm. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L1>
			<L2>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Shocking Grasp</s_name>
					<s_text>When the magic-user casts this spell, he or she develops a powerful electrical charge which gives a jolt to the creature touched. The Shocking Grasp delivers from 1 to 8 hit points damage (d8), plus 1 hit point per level of the magic-user, i.e. a 2nd level magic-user would discharge a shock causing 3 to 10 hit points of damage. While the magic-user must only come close enough to his or her opponent to lay a hand on the opponent's body or upon an electrical conductor which touches the opponent's body, a like touch from the opponent does not discharge the spell. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>I</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L2>
			<L3>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Locate Object</s_name>
					<s_text>This spell aids in location of a known or familiar object. The cleric casts the spell, slowly turns, and knows when he or she is facing in the direction of the object to be located, provided the object is within range, i.e. 7" for 1st level clerics, 8" for 2nd, 9" for 3rd, etc, The casting requires the use of a piece of lodestone, The spell will locate such objects as apparel, jewellery, furniture, tools, weapons, or even a ladder or stairway. By reversal (obscure object), the cleric is able to hide an object from location by spell, crystal ball, or similar means. Neither application of the spell will affect a living creature. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.2</s_cast>
					<s_dura>n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L3>
			<L4>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Enlarge</s_name>
					<s_text> This spell causes instant growth of a creature or object. Enlargement causes increase in both size and weight. It can be cast upon only a single creature or object. Spell range is ½" for each level of experience of the magic-user, and its duration is 1 turn per level of power experience of the spell caster . The effect of the enlargement spell is to increase the size of a living creature (or a symbiotic or community entity) by 20% per level of experience of the magic-user, with a maximum additional growth of 200%. The effect on objects is one-half that of creatures, i.e. 10% per level to a 100% maximum additional enlargement. The creature or object must be seen in order to effect the spell. The maximum volume of living material which can be initially affected is 10 cubic feet - for non-living matter, 5 cubic feet - per level of the magic-user. While magical properties are not increased by this spell - a huge +1 sword is still only +1, a staff-sized wand is still only capable of its normal functions, a giant-sized potion merely requires a greater fluid intake to make its magical effects operate, etc. - weight, mass and strength are. Thus, a table blocking a door would be heavier and more effective; a hurled stone would have more mass (and be more hurtful providing enlargement took place just prior to impact): chains would be more massive; doors thicker; a thin line turned to a sizable, longer rope; and so on. Likewise, a person 12' tall would be as an ogre, while an 18' tall person would actually be a giant for the duration of the spell. The reverse spell, Reduce, will negate the effects or actually make creatures or objects smaller in the tame ratios as the regular spell application functions. Unwilling victims of the spell. or its reverse, are entitled to a saving throw, which, if successful, indicates the magic does not function, and the spell is wasted. The material component of this spell is a pinch of powdered iron.  </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>10n</s_dura>
					<s_save>Neg.</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Detect Invisibility</s_name>
					<s_text> When the magic-user casts a Detect Invisibility spell, he or she is able to clearly see any objects which are invisible, as well as astral, ethereal, hidden, invisible or out of phase creatures. Detection is in the magic-user's line of sight along a 1" wide path to the range limit. The material components of this spell are a pinch of talc and a small sprinkling of powdered silver.</s_text>
					<s_cast>0.2</s_cast>
					<s_dura>5n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L4>
			<L5>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Ventriloquism</s_name>
					<s_text> This spell enables the magic-user to make it sound as if his or her voice - or someone's voice or similar sound - is issuing from someplace else, such as from another creature, a statue, from behind a door, down a passage, etc. The spell caster is able to make his or her voice sound as if a different creature were speaking or making the noise; of course, in a language known by him or her, or a sound which the caster can normally make. With respect to such voices and sounds, there is a 10% chance per point of intelligence above 12 of the hearer that the ruse will be recognized. The material component of the spell is a small cone of parchment. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2+n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Invisibility, r=10'</s_name>
					<s_text> This spell causes a sphere of a radius equalling 10', with a touched creature at its origin, to vanish from sight and not be detectable by normal vision or even infravision. Affected creatures cannot see each other. Of course, the invisible creature(s) is(are) not magically silenced with respect to noises normal to it. The spell remains In effect until it is magically broken or dispelled, or the magic-user or the target cancels it or until he, she or it attacks any creature. Affected creatures only break their own invisibility by attacking, but if the target creature breaks invisibility the entire spell fails. Thus, the spell caster or recipient could open doors, talk, eat, climb stairs, etc., but if any form of attack is made, the invisible creature immediately becomes visible, although this will allow the first attack by the creature because of the former invisibility. Even the allies of the spell recipient cannot see the invisible creature, or his, her or its gear, unless these allies can normally see invisible things or employ magic to do so. Note that all highly intelligent creatures with 10 or more hit dice, or levels of experience, or the equivalent in intelligence/dice/levels have a chance to automatically detect invisible objects. The material components of the Invisibility spell are an eyelash and a bit of gum arabic, the former encased in the latter.</s_text>
					<s_cast>0.3</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Special</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L5>
		</spells>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Cleric</class>
			<race>Half-Elf</race>
			<caster>1</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Bernye Meara</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>41</age>
			<ht>68</ht>
			<wt>102</wt>
			<align>Chaotic Evil</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>13</STR>
			<CON>8</CON>
			<INT>13</INT>
			<WIS>9</WIS>
			<DEX>16</DEX>
			<CHA>12</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>10</pois1>
				<pois2>10</pois2>
				<pois3>10</pois3>
				<pois4>9</pois4>
				<pois5>9</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>13</petr1>
				<petr2>13</petr2>
				<petr3>13</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>13</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>15</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>15</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>1</hp1>
				<hp2>3</hp2>
				<hp3>10</hp3>
				<hp4>12</hp4>
				<hp5>17</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>18</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>5</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>-2</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>4</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Pickaxe</item>
				<item>Bag of Shot</item>
				<item>Heavy Flail</item>
				<item>Ring Mail</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>120</gold>
			<wdie>d12</wdie>
		</props>
		<spells>
			<L1>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Detect Evil </s_name>
					<s_text>This is a spell which discovers emanations of evil, or of good in the case of the reverse spell, from any creature or object. For example, evil alignment or an evilly cursed object will radiate evil, but a hidden trop or an unintelligent viper will not. The duration of a Detect Evil (or Detect Good) spell is 1 turn + ½ turn (5 rounds, or 5 minutes) per level of the cleric. Thus a cleric of 1st level of experience can cast a spell with a 1½ turn duration, at 2nd level a 2 turn duration, 2½ at 3rd, etc. The spell has a path of detection 1" wide in the direction in which the cleric is facing. It requires the use of the cleric's holy (or unholy) symbol as its material component, with the cleric holding it before him or her. </s_text>
					<s_cast>1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>10+5n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L1>
			<L2>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Sanctuary </s_name>
					<s_text>When the cleric casts a Sanctuary spell, any opponent must make a saving throw versus magic in order to strike or otherwise attack him or her. If the saving throw is not made, the creature will attack another and totally ignore the cleric protected by the spell. If the saving throw is made, the cleric is subject to normal attack process including dicing for weapons to hit, saving throws, damage. Note that this spell does not prevent the operation of area attacks (Fireball, Ice Storm, etc.). During the period of protection afforded by this spell, the cleric cannot take offensive action, but he or she may use non-attack spells or otherwise act in any way which does not violate the prohibition against offensive action, This allows the cleric to heal wounds, for example, or to bless, perform an augury, chant, cast a light in the area (not upon on opponent!), and so on, The components of the spell include the cleric's holy/unholy symbol and a small silver mirror. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.4</s_cast>
					<s_dura>2+n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L2>
			<L3>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Slow Poison</s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is placed upon a poisoned individual it greatly slows the effects of any venom, even causing a supposedly dead individual to have life restored if it is cast upon the victim within a number of turns less than or equal to the level of experience of the cleric after the poisoning was suffered. i.e. a victim poisoned up to 10 turns previously could be temporarily saved by a 10th or higher level cleric who cast Slow Poison upon the victim. While this spell does not neutralize the venom, it does prevent it from substantially harming the individual for the duration of its magic, but each turn the poisoned creature will lose 1 hit point from the effect of the venom (although the victim will never go below 1 hit point while the Slow Poison spell's duration lasts). Thus, in the example above, the victim poisoned 10 turns previously has only 10 hit points, so when the 10th level cleric casts the spell, the victim remains with 1 hit point until the spell duration expires, and hopefully during that period a full cure can be accomplished. The material components of this spell are the cleric's holy/unholy symbol and a bud of garlic which must be crushed and smeared on the victim's bare feet. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.1</s_cast>
					<s_dura>60n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L3>
			<L4>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Protection From Evil </s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is cast, it acts as if it were a magical armour upon the recipient. The protection encircles the recipient at a one foot distance, thus preventing bodily contact by creatures of an enchanted or conjured nature such as aerial servants, demons, devils, djinn, efreet, elementals, imps, invisible stalkers, night hags, quasits, salamanders, water weirds, wind walkers, and xorn. Summoned animals or monsters are similarly hedged from the protected creature. Furthermore, any and all attacks launched by evil creatures incur a penalty of -2 from dice rolls "to hit" the protected creature, and any saving throws caused by such attacks are made at +2 on the protected creature's dice. This spell can be reversed to become Protection From Good, although it still keeps out enchanted evil creatures as well. To complete this spell, the cleric must truce a 3' diameter circle upon the floor (or ground) with holy water for Protection From Evil, with blood for Protection From Good - or in the air using burning incense or smouldering dung with respect to evil/good. </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.4</s_cast>
					<s_dura>5n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Chant </s_name>
					<s_text>By means of the chant, the cleric brings into being a special favour upon himself or herself and his or her party, and causes harm to his or her enemies. Once the Chant spell is completed, all attacks, damage and saving throws made by those in the area of effect who are friendly to the cleric are at +1, while those of the cleric's enemies are at -1. This bonus/penalty continues as long as the cleric continues to chant the mystic syllables and is stationary. An interruption, however, such as an attack which succeeds and causes damage, grappling the chanter, or a magical silence, will break the spell. </s_text>
					<s_cast>10</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Special</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L4>
			<L5>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Resist Fire</s_name>
					<s_text>When this spell is placed upon a creature by a cleric, the creature's body is toughened to withstand heat, and boiling temperature is comfortable. The recipient of the resist tire spell can even stand in the midst of very hot or magical fires such as those produced by red-hot charcoal, a large amount of burning oil, flaming swords, fire storms, fire balls, meteor swarms. or red dragon's breath - but these will affect the creature, to some extent. The recipient of the spell gains a bonus of +3 an saving throws against such attack forms, and all damage sustained is reduced by 50%; therefore, if the saving throw is not made, the creature sustains one-half damage, and if the saving throw is mode only one-quarter damage is sustained, Resistance to fire lasts for 1 turn for each level of experience of the cleric placing the spell. The caster needs a drop of mercury as the material component of this spell.  </s_text>
					<s_cast>0.5</s_cast>
					<s_dura>10n</s_dura>
					<s_save>None</s_save>
				</spell>
				<spell>
					<s_name>Glyph of Warding</s_name>
					<s_text>A Glyph of Warding is a powerful inscription magically drawn to prevent unauthorized or hostile creatures from passing, entering, or opening. It can be used to guard a small bridge, ward an entry, or as a trap on a chest or box. When the spell is cast, the cleric weaves a tracery of faintly glowing lines around the warding sigil. For every square foot of area to be protected, 1 segment of time is required to trace the warding lines from the glyph, plus the initial segment during which the sigil itself is traced. A maximum of a 5' X 5' area per level can be warded. When the spell is completed, the glyph and tracery become invisible, but any creature touching the protected area without first speaking the name of the glyph the cleric has used to serve as a ward will be subject to the magic it stores. Saving throws apply, and will either reduce effects by one-half or negate them according to the glyph employed. The cleric must use incense to trace this spell, and then sprinkle the area with powdered diamond (at least 2,000 g.p. worth) if it exceeds 50 square feet. Typical glyphs shock for 2 points of electrical damage per level of the spell caster, explode for a like amount of fire damage, paralyze, blind, or even drain a life energy level (if the cleric is of high enough level to cast this glyph). </s_text>
					<s_cast>Special</s_cast>
					<s_dura>Permanent</s_dura>
					<s_save>Special</s_save>
				</spell>
			</L5>
		</spells>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Thief</class>
			<race>Gnome</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>1</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Menard Matz</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>88</age>
			<ht>41</ht>
			<wt>75</wt>
			<align>Lawful Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>12</STR>
			<CON>15</CON>
			<INT>10</INT>
			<WIS>3</WIS>
			<DEX>9</DEX>
			<CHA>11</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>13</pois1>
				<pois2>13</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>12</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>12</petr1>
				<petr2>12</petr2>
				<petr3>12</petr3>
				<petr4>12</petr4>
				<petr5>11</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>14</wand1>
				<wand2>14</wand2>
				<wand3>14</wand3>
				<wand4>14</wand4>
				<wand5>12</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>16</brea1>
				<brea2>16</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>15</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>16</spel1>
				<spel2>16</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>15</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>1</hp1>
				<hp2>2</hp2>
				<hp3>4</hp3>
				<hp4>8</hp4>
				<hp5>14</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>20</thac03>
				<thac04>20</thac04>
				<thac05>19</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>7</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-3</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>4</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>50' Rope</item>
				<item>Shovel</item>
				<item>Light Crossbow</item>
				<item>Studded Leather Armor</item>
				<item>30 Crossbow Bolts</item>
				<item>Quiver</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>80</gold>
			<wdie>d6</wdie>
		</props>
		<skills>
			<pockets>
				<pock1>15</pock1>
				<pock2>20</pock2>
				<pock3>25</pock3>
				<pock4>30</pock4>
				<pock5>35</pock5>
			</pockets>
			<locks>
				<lock1>20</lock1>
				<lock2>24</lock2>
				<lock3>28</lock3>
				<lock4>32</lock4>
				<lock5>37</lock5>
			</locks>
			<traps>
				<trap1>20</trap1>
				<trap2>25</trap2>
				<trap3>30</trap3>
				<trap4>35</trap4>
				<trap5>40</trap5>
			</traps>
			<sneak>
				<sneak1>0</sneak1>
				<sneak2>6</sneak2>
				<sneak3>12</sneak3>
				<sneak4>18</sneak4>
				<sneak5>25</sneak5>
			</sneak>
			<hide>
				<hide1>5</hide1>
				<hide2>10</hide2>
				<hide3>15</hide3>
				<hide4>20</hide4>
				<hide5>26</hide5>
			</hide>
			<listen>
				<listen1>20</listen1>
				<listen2>20</listen2>
				<listen3>25</listen3>
				<listen4>25</listen4>
				<listen5>30</listen5>
			</listen>
			<climb>
				<climb1>70</climb1>
				<climb2>71</climb2>
				<climb3>72</climb3>
				<climb4>73</climb4>
				<climb5>75</climb5>
			</climb>
			<read>
				<read1>0</read1>
				<read2>0</read2>
				<read3>0</read3>
				<read4>20</read4>
				<read5>25</read5>
			</read>
		</skills>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Fighter</class>
			<race>Human</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Jedda Revan</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>17</age>
			<ht>69</ht>
			<wt>147</wt>
			<align>Lawful Good</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>9</STR>
			<CON>14</CON>
			<INT>10</INT>
			<WIS>13</WIS>
			<DEX>6</DEX>
			<CHA>11</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>11</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>15</petr1>
				<petr2>15</petr2>
				<petr3>14</petr3>
				<petr4>14</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>16</wand1>
				<wand2>16</wand2>
				<wand3>15</wand3>
				<wand4>15</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>17</brea1>
				<brea2>17</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>13</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>17</spel1>
				<spel2>17</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>13</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>4</hp1>
				<hp2>6</hp2>
				<hp3>7</hp3>
				<hp4>15</hp4>
				<hp5>22</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>16</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>5</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-6</armorac>
				<dexac>1</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>1</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Small pouch</item>
				<item>Pint of Ale</item>
				<item>Dagger</item>
				<item>Banded Armor</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>90</gold>
			<wdie>d4</wdie>
		</props>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Fighter</class>
			<race>Half-Elf</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Caedmon Arnetta</name>
			<gender>&#x2640;</gender>			<age>26</age>
			<ht>64</ht>
			<wt>100</wt>
			<align>Chaotic Good</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>9</STR>
			<CON>4</CON>
			<INT>13</INT>
			<WIS>12</WIS>
			<DEX>12</DEX>
			<CHA>14</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>11</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>15</petr1>
				<petr2>15</petr2>
				<petr3>14</petr3>
				<petr4>14</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>16</wand1>
				<wand2>16</wand2>
				<wand3>15</wand3>
				<wand4>15</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>17</brea1>
				<brea2>17</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>13</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>17</spel1>
				<spel2>17</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>13</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>1</hp1>
				<hp2>4</hp2>
				<hp3>12</hp3>
				<hp4>15</hp4>
				<hp5>24</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>16</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>8</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-2</armorac>
				<dexac>0</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>1</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Flask of Oil</item>
				<item>Candles (5)</item>
				<item>Heavy Flail</item>
				<item>Leather Armor</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>70</gold>
			<wdie>d12</wdie>
		</props>
	</character>
	<character>
		<base>
			<class>Fighter</class>
			<race>Halfling</race>
			<caster>0</caster>
			<skilled>0</skilled>
			<xp>
				<xp1>0</xp1>
				<xp2>0</xp2>
				<xp3>0</xp3>
				<xp4>0</xp4>
				<xp5>0</xp5>
			</xp>
			<features>
			</features>
		</base>
		<fluff>
			<name>Ewanne Cloryan</name>
			<gender>&#x2642;</gender>			<age>26</age>
			<ht>40</ht>
			<wt>57</wt>
			<align>Neutral</align>
		</fluff>
		<stats>
			<STR>13</STR>
			<CON>9</CON>
			<INT>11</INT>
			<WIS>7</WIS>
			<DEX>16</DEX>
			<CHA>14</CHA>
		</stats>
		<saves>
			<poison>
				<pois1>14</pois1>
				<pois2>14</pois2>
				<pois3>13</pois3>
				<pois4>13</pois4>
				<pois5>11</pois5>
			</poison>
			<petrify>
				<petr1>15</petr1>
				<petr2>15</petr2>
				<petr3>14</petr3>
				<petr4>14</petr4>
				<petr5>12</petr5>
			</petrify>
			<wand>
				<wand1>16</wand1>
				<wand2>16</wand2>
				<wand3>15</wand3>
				<wand4>15</wand4>
				<wand5>13</wand5>
			</wand>
			<breath>
				<brea1>17</brea1>
				<brea2>17</brea2>
				<brea3>16</brea3>
				<brea4>16</brea4>
				<brea5>13</brea5>
			</breath>
			<spell>
				<spel1>17</spel1>
				<spel2>17</spel2>
				<spel3>16</spel3>
				<spel4>16</spel4>
				<spel5>13</spel5>
			</spell>
		</saves>
		<attrib>
			<hpval>
				<hp1>6</hp1>
				<hp2>15</hp2>
				<hp3>19</hp3>
				<hp4>28</hp4>
				<hp5>35</hp5>
			</hpval>
			<thac0>
				<thac01>20</thac01>
				<thac02>20</thac02>
				<thac03>18</thac03>
				<thac04>18</thac04>
				<thac05>16</thac05>
			</thac0>
			<damage>0</damage>
			<ac>
				<totalac>6</totalac>
				<shieldac>0</shieldac>
				<armorac>-2</armorac>
				<dexac>-2</dexac>
			</ac>
			<doors>2</doors>
			<lgbb>4</lgbb>
		</attrib>
		<props>
			<invlist>
				<item>Iron Nails (15)</item>
				<item>Silver Mirror</item>
				<item>Broadsword</item>
				<item>Leather Armor</item>
			</invlist>
			<gold>60</gold>
			<wdie>d8</wdie>
		</props>
	</character>
</chargen>
